<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AutoLockToggle</string>
    <string name="locktime_tile">Automatic Lock</string>
    <string name="intro">Welcome to AutoLockToggle!\n\nImmediate screen lock upon power button press usually comes in handy to prevent your phone from going crazy in your pocket. However, when mounted to a bicycle or car phone mount, you might want to turn off the screen and re-enable it without having to unlock while riding a bumpy road.\n\nAutoLockToggle adds a quick settings tile allowing you to quickly change Android\'s automatic screen lock timer from 0 seconds to minutes and vice versa.\n\nReady? To use the app, few settings need to be adjusted. The following pages will guide you through the setup.</string>
    <string name="desc0">AutoLockToggle relies on changing the automatic lock timer, which is considered to be an Android security system setting.\n\nOn non-rooted devices, the permissions needed for changing these can only be granted by connecting your device to a computer with Android Debugging Bridge installed and running the following command:</string>
    <string name="desc1">Second, open the automatic lock settings and disable instant lock on power button press.</string>
    <string name="desc2">Select AutoLockToggle from the list in the modify system settings dialog and allow modifying system settings.</string>
    <string name="desc3">Open the quick settings menu by sliding down twice from the top of your screen.\n\nHit the pencil icon and drag the AutoLockToggle tile to a position of your choice.\n\nEnjoy your new AutoLockToggle tile!</string>
    <string name="action_configure_timer">Configure Lock Timer Interval</string>
    <string name="dialog_configure_timer">Specify the timer interval used whenever immediate automatic lock is disabled</string>
    <string name="locktime_hint">Lock time in seconds</string>
    <string name="locktime_unit">s</string>
    <string name="locktime_key">locktime_s</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
</resources>